Have you ever heard about that
the cliff of a snow mountain
once fascinated numerous people?
Legend has it that,
there were treasures at the peak
but also there was a bottomless chasm hidden over there.
The smart, the fool
and the kind people,
all are familiar to you.
On the mountainside, on the cliff,
on the cloud,
and in the human world,
snowflakes are drifting profusely and disorderly.
Joy of Life Season 1
Episode 20
Prime Minister, what do you mean?
If I keep thinking of him,
how could I focus on supporting you?
Now that it has happened,
you have to be careful of the Crown Prince.
Do you think
he wants to kill me?
There are two reasons.
First,
you'll take over Neiku
from Li Yunrui.
She is Wan'er's birth mother.
I didn't mean to offend her.
Second,
you've been supporting the Second Prince
since you came to the capital city.
The Crown Prince is not happy about that.
I just met the Second Prince a few times.
I'm not his supporter.
You should have avoided seeing him.
The capital city is a dangerous place.
If you didn't choose to support someone,
it could
lead to your doom.
What should I do?
From now on, remain neutral.
Try your best
to avoid seeing either of them.
But you just said
I should choose to support someone.
Now that you're my son-in-law,
you'll be on my side.
But if the Crown Prince holds a grudge against me,
I'm afraid you'll get into trouble because of me
when he succeeds to the throne.
I'll try to act as a mediator.
If he keeps treating you as an enemy,
I'll help
someone else
succeed to the throne.
It turns out it's not blue
when there is little water.
But I've never seen the sea.
I can take you to see it in the future.
Elder brother, are you done talking?
Dabao,
I'm going to marry your younger sister.
So, you'll be my elder brother.
Are you going to marry Wan'er?
Yeah.
She's a nice girl.
She's never scolded me.
Besides,
She...
She also treats me on cakes.
I'll treat you on cakes too.
Really?
Yes.
So,
will you take me to see the sea?
Sure.
We have to
take Wan'er with us.
Go!
Hi, Mr. Yuan.
Let's go.
Trust me.
I'll take Wan'er with me no matter where I go.
That would be great.
How about Erbao?
What?
Shall we
take Erbao with us?
Dabao,
Erbao
has gone somewhere far far away.
You probably won't see him for a long time.
Is he dead?
I once raised kittens
and bunnies.
But they were gone later.
I looked,
looked,
and looked for them.
But I failed to find them.
A maidservant told me
they're dead.
I asked Wan'er what it means.
She said
it means
they've gone somewhere far far away
and I won't see them
for a long, long time.
Someday,
I'll also go there.
Then I'll see them again.
So, in the future,
I'll go to
that faraway place.
I'll see my kittens,
my bunnies
and Erbao.
When I see them again,
I...
I'll tell them
it has been a long time and I miss them.
Okay. You can say that.
Wan'er also likes to
touch my head like this.
It's comfortable.
Elder brother,
the two of you are quite alike.
Dabao,
I told you you'll be my elder brother.
Listen to me.
Don't call me like that again.
Are you younger than me?
Yeah. I'm younger than you.
Call me Fan Xian.
Fan...
Can I call you Xianxian?
Dabao,
this name
sounds weird.
Xianxian.
Don't call me like that.
-Xianxian. -Stop calling me like that.
Xianxian! Xianxian! Xianxian!
I've told the Crown Prince about it.
He didn't say anything.
It's okay as long as he knew it.
Your Excellency,
Are you sure
you'll entrust the future of your daughter and your clan
to Fan Xian?
I saw
Fan Xian play with Dabao.
So did I.
Actually,
even the servants in my mansion
will laugh at Dabao
behind my back
when they see him.
I know most of them
look down upon him
and are impatient with talking to him.
But Fan Xian smiled from the bottom of his heart
when he stayed with Dabao.
It's true.
It seems Fan Xian treats Dabao
as his friend.
In that very moment,
I decided to
rely on him for our future
if he has nothing to do
with Gong'er's death.
Alright. Let's say goodbye here.
Go back. I'll come some other day.
You were not called in by my dad.
What?
Those who are called in by my dad
don't like to play with me.
They only smile at me
when dad is around.
They ignore me
if dad is not around.
Did you tell your dad
about it?
No.
You can't!
I'm telling you.
You can't tell my dad.
If you do,
he'll scold them
and they'll feel depressed.
Dabao,
do you know how long
I've been in the capital city?
No.
Since I came here from Danzhou,
I've met many people and
many things have happened.
But in my opinion,
you're more lovely
than most of them.
Danzhou?
Do you mean I'm a good guy?
Yes, you're.
Xianxian, remember
to often come play with me.
I told you not to call...
Okay. I promise.
Then, go home.
If you don't,
your dad will also scold you.
I'm leaving.
Remember.
Don't pick up food
that's thrown away by others.
Got it.
Don't jump in puddles.
Don't grab others' candy.
Got it.
And,
remember
to put on clothes before you go out.
Got it.
Remember
to use chopsticks when you have a meal.
Don't eat with your hands.
Got it.
Your Excellency.
Why is it you again?
Of course it's me.
Are you expecting someone else?
You told me
to send your sister to the Eastern Palace.
The Crown Prince didn't come to
the Prime Minister Mansion to catch me.
Yeah.
Lady Ruoruo stayed there for a long time
before she came out.
I'd been waiting for her.
She said
it's too slow to come over in a sedan chair.
She asked me to come here first.
What's the matter?
The Crown Prince left.
He might have gone to the bathroom.
Please don't crack a joke.
He didn't go to the bathroom.
He left the Eastern Palace.
I see. It's a serious matter.
Where is he going?
The Investigator's Office.
Why does he want to go there?
Lady Ruoruo said
he's going to see Si Lili.
Your Highness, are you going to
the Investigator's Office to see Si Lili?
Yes.
You don't need to follow me there.
Your Highness,
you don't believe what Mr. Yuan said, right?
I don't believe what Si Lili said.
So, are you going to interrogate her again?
On the contrary,
I'm going to save her.
He wants to save Si Lili.
Lady Ruoruo also asked the Crown Prince
why he wants to do that.
He said,
now that
you interrogated Si Lili alone,
it means it's possible
you've known Lin Gong's issue,
but you told Si Lili
not to tell anyone else about it.
Why would Si Lili
listen to my brother?
Why would she rather suffer cruel torture
than tell the truth?
Because Fan Xian
would promise to spare her life in return
if she keeps the secret.
I'll never break my promise.
Tell me his name
and I'll keep you safe.
Lady Ruoruo wanted me to ask you
if you promised
to keep Si Lili safe
just as the Crown Prince said.
I want you to trust me.
I am the only one
who is willing to keep you alive
in the capital city now.
Okay.
Your Excellency.
What else did the Crown Prince say?
He said
he'd swear in the name of his identity as the Crown Prince
he'd get Si Lili out of the dungeon
and keep her safe
if she tells the truth.
Let's go to the Investigator's Office.
Your Excellency, don't panic so much.
Maybe Miss Si Lili
is still passionately devoted to you
and refuses to say anything.
Si Lili wouldn't
tell the truth
just for one reason,
that is, she knows that
the Investigator's Office thinks highly of me.
So, she wouldn't tell the truth
as long as she's imprisoned
in the Investigator's Office.
If she knows the Crown Prince would save her...
She'll sell me down the river.
If Si Lili tells the truth,
the Crown Prince, the Prime Minister
and even His Majesty
would think
it's me that killed Lin Gong.
It's too late.
Your Excellency, you have to find a way
to stop the Crown Prince.
If I stand out at this moment,
it means I admit I did everything.
I have an idea.
I'll try to delay the Crown Prince
and you go to the dungeon
and kill Si Lili.
I promised not to kill her.
It's urgent.
You'll die if she's alive.
But it's of no use to kill her.
If Si Lili is killed at this moment,
it just proves I want to do away with a witness.
We can say
it's the secret agents from Beiqi that did it.
Do you know why the Crown Prince
told Ruoruo the reason
why he'd come to the Investigator's Office?
Why?
Because he has never believed
Ruoruo would support himself.
He told her about it
just to let her send word to me
so that I'd respond.
So, what can we do to solve the dilemma?
I just hope
someone can stop him
from entering the Investigator's Office,
or I'll come to the end of a blind alley.
But the Crown Prince is so powerful.
Wait. There is still hope.
His Majesty once said
Their Highnesses shall not meddle
in the Investigator's Office's affairs.
Besides,
the directors of divisions
wouldn't let him in.
I hope so.
There they are.
Line up!
Mr. Zhu, please step aside.
Your Highness, His Majesty said
princes can't come inside.
Do you want to stop me?
He wants to stop me.
I dare not.
It's His Majesty's order. I hardly dare disobey it.
Okay.
From now on,
I'll start to go inside.
And I won't stop
unless
you take actions.
Your Highness, if you insist on doing it,
His Majesty will fly into a rage.
Do you dare to take actions?
The Investigator's Office is of great importance.
It's the lifeblood of the imperial court.
Your Highness, if you step forward again,
I'll draw my sword.
I just dare not disobey His Majesty's order.
I'll have no other choice
but to knock you out
and then take you to His Majesty.
I see.
Do you think you can
stop my picked guards
by yourself alone?
Draw your swords!
Your Highness, here is the capital city.
How will you explain it to His Majesty?
Lin Gong is my good friend.
For both private and public reasons,
I'll find out the truth.
The Investigator's Office will do it.
I don't trust you.
Step aside!
The Crown Prince is so tough.
I'm dead.
His Excellency Yan and His Excellency Zhu.
are trying to stop him.
They couldn't do it.
I've underestimated the Crown Prince.
Such being the case,
all our plans in the capital city will come to nothing.
Wang Qinian,
I'll find a way
to get out of the capital city.
You just pretend
you know nothing about it.
They won't make things difficult for you.
Your Excellency.
Farewell, Wang Qinian.
-Step aside! -Listen.
What's the noise?
Go!
Black knights!
Disarm them.
-Head. -Head.
What's wrong?
I've got a cold.
I'll send for an imperial physician.
Don't bother.
=Chen Pingping, Head of the Investigator's Office=
What happened to his legs?
That very year,
Head Chen travelled hundreds of miles
with black knights
and defeated Xiao En,
the No.1 villain of Beiqi.
However, he was injured during that battle
and couldn't walk since then.
Your Highness, please go back.
Go away!
Chen Pingping, you're so powerful.
Someone said
you're only second to one person in the capital city.
Your Highness, you misheard it.
I've heard black knights
are good at fighting and have killed numerous people.
Do they dare to kill a Crown Prince?
Or will you do it yourself?
Attacking a Crown Prince
is not something a loyal subject should do.
Then you couldn't stop me.
Go away!
He's so tough.
What are you doing?
Go away!
Protect His Highness.
Chen Pingping!
Let go of me.
Protecting Crown Prince
against assassinations
is what a loyal subject should do.
Master Shadow.
Head wants to see you.
I've been thinking about
why black knights showed up at that time
when I chased Si Lili out of town.
How did they know
about my whereabouts?
Seeing you throw a dagger,
I finally understand.
It's true that Head asked me
to stay and serve you.
It's also you that sent secret messages
to black knights, right?
He and I
are closest to Head.
You can leave. I'll tell him everything.
Got it.
You prove yourself to be Head of the Investigator's Office.
Nobody else could be
more scheming and calculating than you.
Push me in.
Why are you looking at me? Anything on my face?
Come closer.
You should wear more. Don't catch a cold.
You have her eyes.
At that time, she just stood there.
I asked her
what flowers she wanted to plant
when the Investigator's Office was just set up.
I'd find them no matter how precious they are
as long as she told me.
She scattered those wildflower seeds
she got by the roadside
alongside the wall at random.
She said,
we didn't need to grow flowers
because these seeds
would find their own way of living.
Who is she?
Ye Qingmei. Your mother.
Who's Ye Qingmei?
Wuzhu is in the capital city?
Who is Wuzhu?
He killed Lin Gong.
The truth hasn't been found out
about Lin Gong's death.
You don't believe me.
It's alright.
I'll take care of the rest about Lin Gong's issue.
The Imperial Study
Your Highness.
I want to see His Majesty.
Your Highness, what's the matter?
Your Majesty,
His Highness wants to see you.
He said
he guessed
the real murderer
who killed Lin Gong.
Who does he think it is?
I hardly dare say.
I'm not asking for your opinion.
Just repeat his words.
His Highness said
it's probably the Second Prince.
Your Excellency Wang, why are you sitting here?
Your Excellency,
please don't call me like that.
You're a trusted follower of Head.
You're closest to him.
I'll have to rely on you
in the Investigator's Office.
Your Excellency, please don't say that.
Actually,
we just made a deal.
What is it?
Your Excellency.
Your Excellency. Your Excellency.
Actually,
I planned to quit the Investigator's Office,
but Head Chen
offered me something
and asked me to stay and serve you
before he came back to the capital city.
At first,
I didn't plan to accept it.
But since I met you at the gate of the capital city,
I began to think about it.
Later on,
I watched you for several days.
I found
you're not only handsome and brave,
but also noble-minded.
I admire you so much
that I decided to
stay here
and serve you.
Tell me the truth.
You're generous with your money.
That's why I admire you.
Why did you want to quit?
Over the years,
the Investigator's Office has done a lot
and readjusted the administration of officials.
I'd have a bright future
if I stay here.
But I don't think
I still have
the ambition.
I don't want to be promoted again.
Speaking of it, maybe I'm too soft-hearted
to bear the sight of
those harsh punishments.
Is it by Chen Pingping's order?
Of course not.
Head once said
such torture can be used
to deal with enemies,
but should never be used on one of us.
Nobody would listen to him?
There is something you don't know.
Nowadays,
there are more and more people
who're willing to die for Nanqing.
They're so loyal
that they can't tolerate
a little mistake.
Then they've become
more and more ruthless.
Even Head
can dare not criticize such loyalty.
I'm lazy by nature.
I failed to change with the times.
I failed to keep pace with them.
So,
I wanted to quit.
Where are you
going in the future?
Where could I go?
Of course
I'll keep serving you.
I see. I see.
I did lie to you.
I'll do something to show my apology.
What are you going to do?
Hold on.
What are you doing?
Your Excellency.
I'll treat you on tasty food. It's on me.
Let's go enjoy ourselves.
Hold on.
I don't have enough money.
I'll pay for 1.5 bowls of noodles.
Can you give me two bowls?
No. No way.
I'm not done talking. Look.
Only one bowl
with minced meat.
Just add some soup
to the other bowl.
Is it okay?
Okay.
You're flexible enough.
Your Excellency.
Here you are.
Okay.
It looks small in size,
but the taste is very special.
Enjoy it. I've paid for it.
The two bowls of noodles look different.
You're right.
The essence of the noodles
lies in the soup.
You'll know its original taste and flavor like this.
All the extra toppings
have been omitted.
They're omitted.
Come on.
Eat while they're hot.
These toppings are unnecessary.
Chen Pingping
is a monster from Heaven.
He looks different from us.
Humans
have two eyes,
but Chen Pingping
has three more eyes
between the two like ours.
Most of us have two arms,
but Chen Pingping
has two more on his back.
With edged tools in his hands, he's awe-inspiring.
Five eyes?
Four arms?
Exactly.
His Excellency Chen
is over three meters high.
His face looks like a door plank
and his fist like a hammer.
He has a large, fierce-looking mouth.
When he shouts at the town,
a roll of thunder
will crash in the sky immediately.
Every night,
Chen Pingping would go to the army barracks of Beiqi
and eat over ten soldiers.
Having got used to it,
the Beiqi forces draw lots
to wait to be eaten by him.
Dear all, in a word,
Chen Pingping is brave and battlewise
and can even move mountains.
How do you like it, Your Excellency?
Not bad.
So, you've forgiven me, right?
I have to think about it.
Let me get you more soup.
Okay?
That's enough.
Young Master.
Why are you still here eating?
Why are you here?
I just listened to stories in the tea house.
Why did you go there?
Our bookstore
is going to open.
Why are you so neglectful?
We should spend more time
collecting relevant information.
I just heard a new story.
"Chen Pingping
Travelled Hundreds of Miles to Beiqi Alone."
It's amazing.
If you write a book about it,
it'll definitely sell well.
Chen Pingping?
Travelled hundreds of miles?
Alone.
Eunuch Hou.
Mr. Fan.
His Majesty wants to see you. It's urgent.
I'm not done with the noodles.
There is no time for delay.
They're all waiting for you.
Eunuch Hou, how did you know I was there?
You were not at home,
so I went to the Investigator's Office.
Head Chen told me you were there.
Chen Pingping?
The Investigator's Office
can find anyone
in the capital city easily.
He found me so quickly.
He must have sent someone to tail after me.
Mr. Fan,
what Head Chen wants to do
is not something we should think about.
Young Master,
your brother said
he'd treat me on noodles,
but he left
before he paid.
Can you give the money to me?
I'll pay for it.
How much?
Three taels of silver.
Three taels?
Yeah. It's cheap.
For the two bowls of noodles?
Even without meat.
It's profitable.
More profitable than opening a bookstore.
How about like this?
I'll buy the store
tomorrow.
The money you paid today will be considered your shares.
Great! I'll make a fortune.
He wouldn't even pay a cent.
Mr. Fan, hold on please.
Let me tell His Majesty about it.
Prime Minister.
I saw you from the distance.
You have nothing to lose by calling me uncle.
Uncle, you're also here.
His Majesty said
it's something about Gong'er's death.
It's a serious issue.
Shall we talk about it just in the Imperial Study?
With His Majesty there, there will be no room for maneuver.
Prime Minister. Mr. Fan.
This way, please.
Don't be afraid. Follow me.
Your Majesty.
Prime Minister and Mr. Fan are here.
Let them in.
Your Majesty.
They're here.
You can make things clear
in their presence.
Prepare a seat and some tea for Prime Minister.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, how about me?
You?
Just stand here.
Your Highness, you don't need to bow to me.
The Investigator's Office has checked Lin Gong's body.
He was killed by a skilled swordsman with a fast sword.
Among all swordsmen in the capital city,
only Xie Bi'an that works for the Second Prince
has the ability to do that.
Do you mean...
He means
I'm the one who killed Lin Gong.
Are you the killer?
You have to ask Fan Xian about it.
Your Highness,
how is it related to me?
During 9 a.m. to 11 a.m. of the day
when Lin Gong was killed,
I happened to meet Fan Xian on the street
and we had a small talk.
Xie Bi'an was also there.
I just asked you to be here to give witness.
Xie Bi'an is known as
"Faster than Light."
He is the best swordsman
in the capital city.
Faster than light?
Fast sword.
Is it true?
Yes.
The Investigator's Office has confirmed
Lin Gong was killed during 9 a.m. to 11 a.m.
In this case,
Xie Bi'an didn't have enough time
to rush out of town to do that.
There is another possibility.
Fan Xian and you joined hands
to let Xie Bi'an kill Lin Gong.
He was giving false testimony
to help you stay out of it.
It's more ridiculous.
Why did I want to kill Lin Gong?
Why did Fan Xian want to do that?
Lin Gong is the one behind
the assassination attempt on Niulan Street.
Fan Xian holds a grudge against him.
Your Highness,
I have no idea about that.
He's the Crown Prince.
We have to bear it if he wants to declare us guilty.
Then tell me
who else is so skilled at swordsmanship
if it's not Xie Bi'an.
It's not hard
to hire a sword master
who is unrecognized, right?
To whom are you making pointed allusions?
I'm just trying to reason.
It's enough.
Prime Minister,
the victim is your son. What do you think?
In my opinion,
the person to blame
is Chen Pingping.
The Investigator's Office is responsible
for the safety of the capital city.
Up to now, they haven't reported
the truth about my son's death.
It means Chen Pingping
has neglected his duties.
It makes sense.
I hope to
confront Chen Pingping
and see him be punished according to law.
It seems you enjoy standing there.
Your Majesty, shall I kneel down?
Rise.
Send an imperial decree
and ask Chen Pingping to come here.
Got it.
Chen Pingping!
Your Majesty.
Do you know your sin?
Why do you say that?
The Prime Minister's son was killed.
As Head of
the Investigator's Office,
you haven't found out the killer up to now.
You have to take responsibility.
Your Majesty,
we've found out the killer.
You found it out?
Good.
In the presence of Prime Minister and others,
tell me who is the killer.
Prime Minister,
I'm surprised to hear the sad news upon my return.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Who is the killer?
Si Gujian from Dongyi Town.
One of the Great Masters?
If it were not a Great Master,
who else could use a sword so quickly?
As a Great Master,
he travelled hundreds of miles to the capital city
to kill the Prime Minister's son?
Why did he do that?
Lin Gong joined hands with Si Lili
to try to assassinate Fan Xian on Niulan Street,
but Si Gujian lost a disciple and a follower
during the process.
The two female assassinators
were killed by Fan Xian.
Why did Si Gujian kill Lin Gong
to take revenge?
Everyone knows that
Si Gujian is obsessed with swordsmanship.
Fan Xian killed the two assassinators
when he was attacked.
Si Gujian would think highly of him
because of his capabilities.
And he'd only take revenge on
Lin Gong and Beiqi
that are behind all this.
In the river of history,
time goes round and round.
Memories about the former and present lives
join each other in an endless way.
In the long drunken Milky Way,
one season follows another in a flash,
and the wild geese are flying south.
I just can't give up
to be with you for my whole life.
I have been hovering in the dreams
for hundreds and thousands of times.
I can't even say a word when I watch the flowers falling.
Year after year in the wandering,
I count the remaining years.
Even though we can't meet each other anymore,
even though we have ended up the destiny,
I never feel regretful.
In such a chaotic world,
I still miss you as ever.
I can't fall asleep under the moon.
With a gentle heart,
I cherish our remaining years.
Even though we have to go through
all the hardships along the journey,
you always stay by my side,
watching the falling flowers, speechlessly.
Year after year in the wandering,
I count the remaining years.
Even though we can't meet each other anymore,
even though we end up the destiny,
I never feel regretful.
In such a chaotic world,
I still miss you as ever.
I can't fall asleep under the moon.
With a gentle heart,
I cherish our remaining years.
Even though we have to go through
all the hardships along the journey,
you always stay by my side...